

⊕ ABOUT ME

NET Developer passionate about web development where I primarily focus on writing clean, elegant, and efficient code. I have enrolled in Wantsome IT Academy to learn all the stages of .NET web development while allowing me to make a full website with ASP.NET for the final project. This experience has enriched my knowledge of designing and developing applications. NET framework.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

.NET (C#)
SQL
HTML/CSS
Java Script
Photoshop
Illustrator

DERSONAL SKILLS

- Problem-solving
- Communication
- Responsibility
- Teamwork
- Attention to Detail
- Creative

© CONTACT ME

- 0753704360
- vrancianuandrei@gmail.com www.vrancianuandrei.ro
- Jud. Bacău, Bacău, Strada Milcov, Bl. 71, Sc. B, Ap. 2

EDUCATION

2011-2015 HIGH SCHOOL DIPLOMA

COLEGIUL ECONOMIC "ION GHICA" BACĂU

General skills: Romanian language, Mathematics, Business communication, English language, Information and communication technology. Professional skills: Simulated a real business

environment.

2019-2020

.NET PROGRAMMING COURSE

WANTSOME THE FRIENDLY IT ACADEMY IAȘI

General skills: Algorithms, OOP, SQL, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, ASP.NET, ADO.NET.

Professional skills: Website store made with ASP.NET, including Bootstrap and Java Script.

JOB EXPERIENCE

2012-2015 IMAGE DIRECTOR (VOLUNTEER)

LEO CLUB PHOENIX, BACĂU

- Responsible for the image of the group (Facebook page, Logo, etc.);
- Working with people of all ages, economic statuses, cultures, and with various needs;
- Effectively built and directed the promotional materials for events;
- Generated creative ideas and design concepts.

2014-2018 DESIGNER (FREELANCER)

99DESIGNS

- Successfully created and implemented digital graphic design projects from concept through completion;
- Worked closely with the client to create a vision, conceive designs, and consistently meet deadlines and requirements.

2017-2019 SALE CONSULTANT

DEDEMAN, IAŞI

- · Met with key personnel to implement on-going sales planning;
- Design of bathrooms and kitchens in the ViSoft3D program;
- Managed the day to day clientele business to meet marketing objectives, and to help set measurable metrics for success;
- Executed problem-solving skills to determine solutions for clients in any situations.

⊕ COMPUTER SKILLS

- Microsoft Office Suite
- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe Illustrator

- Visual Studio
- Unity3D
- ViSoft3D